[Music]
hi this video explains customer and
partner onboarding Journeys when adding
a new customer to your portfolio it's a
clip from a launch event video for 2023
release Wave 2 but it's equally relevant
today let's turn it over to CERN who
will tell us more about it but first s
is going to tell us a little bit more
about the partner and customer Journey
definitely thank you so much Sarah so
you touched on something important there
which is relevant content and today what
you know as the standard trial
experience that you start on
dynamics.com doesn't really give you
relevant content well not as relevant as
it could be because it's a generic trial
you started on the dynamics.com website
you venture into the Kronos evaluation
company maybe you venture into the
non-evaluation company called my company
and then at some point we hope you'll
contact the Microsoft partner buy your
license or get started somehow with
business Central that's the most
well-known Journey for those who just
Venture into into this on their own and
find our website the other scenario you
know the other Journey that you know is
when when a prospect meets your website
maybe they saw your solution they like
to see a like to get a demo or see that
solution in a trial there's a lot more
friction in that scenario because you
need to First establish the CSP
relationship that uh virtual paperwork
that needs to happen where where you add
the trial skew to the customer and
partner Center you load up BC for them
you load any apps you think are relevant
for your for for that experience and you
load the configuration then you hand
over that experience to the prospect to
the customer and then at some point
hopefully they will continue that
Journey now we can remove the friction
in that while still providing that same
relevance for for the Prospect and this
is relatively new but there's a way to
create a digital experience that has
your Special Sauce in it and now we're
going to show you what that's all about
basically on a timeline it could look
like this it ends with the customer
going live of course but it starts with
you profiling the prospect on your
website because to be able to give the
most relevant experience you need to
know something about that potential
customer like for example what industry
are they in what kind of business are
they running uh maybe what kind of
system are they currently using are they
using Excel or some other competitive
product now that's all relevant because
you want to stage business Central as
being the great new solution for them so
you need to know about what environment
are they operating in right now so after
you profile them you redirect them to
the signup um at uh dynamics.com so
basically we spin up the standard trial
and we load an appsource app that you
have decided which one is the most
relevant one
and the most important thing is here
that whatever the outcome of the profile
was on your website is carried through
that journey and is actually available
in business Central so you can pivot The
Experience based on the preferences the
expectations from that
customer that means that coming back to
the first pillar of our strategy you saw
that being able to be matched with the
partner solution from day Zero is
actually what's taking place here it's a
partner-driven experience at the very
first sign in at the very first meeting
with the product that means to Sarah's
point that you know who wants to go to
the pool and who wants to go straight to
the bar you can serve them with what
they
want so you can build an experience
where the prospect can try out in
Corners you can even build in an
embedded buying experience that will
take care of the CSP uh part of things
and take them through uh the onboarding
piece as well in the their own company
and dynamically load all the data that
this customer needs in terms of chart of
accounts and posting groups and what
have you and then the customer can go
live and your Consultants can then uh
focus on the more complex part of that
of that business to learn more visit
aka.ms BC onboarding thank you for
watching
[Music]